Guide to the John L. Margrave academic papers, 1952-1995 MS 505
Woodson Research Center, Rice University, Houston, Texas
- Series IV: Houston Area Research Center (HARC), 1980-1989, 221617
  - Correspondence, 1983, 221638 (Box 7, Folder 13)
  - Correspondence, 1984-1989, 221637 (Box 7, Folder 14)
  - Executive Committee, Agendas, 221636 (Box 7, Folder 15)
  - Executive Committee, General Correspondence, 221635 (Box 7, Folder 16)
  - Executive Committee, Minutes, 221634 (Box 7, Folder 17)
  - Executive Committee, Miscellaneous, 221633 (Box 7, Folder 18)
  - Financial Information, 221632 (Box 7, Folder 19)
  - Meetings, January 28, 1986, 221631 (Box 7, Folder 20)
  - Meetings, "The Houston Area Research Center", 221630 (Box 7, Folder 21)
  - Meetings, Materials Science, 221629 (Box 7, Folder 22)
  - Meetings, Sodium Advanced Fast Reactor, 221628 (Box 7, Folder 23)
  - Meetings, Strategic Defense Initiative, 221627 (Box 7, Folder 24)
  - Meetings, Supercomputer Applications, 221626 (Box 7, Folder 25)
  - Meetings, White House Fellows, 221625 (Box 7, Folder 26)
  - Miscellaneous, 221624 (Box 7, Folder 27-29)
  - News Releases, 221623 (Box 7, Folder 30)
  - Organizational Charts, 221622 (Box 7, Folder 31)
  - Proposals, 221621 (Box 7, Folder 32-33)
  - Reports, 221620 (Box 7, Folder 34)
  - Superconducting Super Collider, 221619 (Box 7, Folder 35)
  - Superconducting Super Collider, Proposal, 221618 (Box 7, Folder 36)
- Series V: High Temperature Science (HTS), 1967-1995, 221520
  The High Temperature Science (HTS) series is comprised of the papers connected with Margrave's editorship of this scientific journal. Included are the internal paperwork between Margrave and the periodical's contributors, as well as those between Margrave and the two publishing houses, Academic Press and Humana Press. Also included in this series are general correspondence, answers to a questionnaire Margrave developed in connection with the near demise of the journal, and a special tribute written about Margrave by Paul Gilles of the University of Kansas.
  Since the papers generated by Margrave within this series overlap in time, researchers are encouraged to look in folders that lie on either side of the year in which they are interested (that is, if you are interested in a date early in 1974, you should look in the latter part of the 1973 folder as well).
  - Bank Statement, 221616 (Box 8, Folder 1)
  - Correspondence, 1967-1973, 221615 (Box 8, Folder 2)
  - Correspondence, 1974-1975, 221614 (Box 8, Folder 3)
  - Correspondence, 1976, 221613 (Box 8, Folder 4)
  - Correspondence, 1977, 221612 (Box 8, Folder 5)
  - Correspondence, 1978-1979, 221611 (Box 8, Folder 6)
  - Correspondence, 1980s, 221610 (Box 8, Folder 7)
  - Correspondence, 1990s, 221609 (Box 8, Folder 8)
  - Correspondence, Not Dated, 221608 (Box 8, Folder 9)
  - "John L. Margrave: Prolific, Creative, Indefatigable Chemist", 221607 (Box 8, Folder 10)
  - Leo Brewer Issue (1984), General Correspondence, 221606 (Box 8, Folder 11)
  - Leo Brewer Issue, Manuscript B1, 221605 (Box 8, Folder 12)
  - Leo Brewer Issue, Manuscript B2, 221604 (Box 8, Folder 13)
  - Leo Brewer Issue, Manuscript B3, 221603 (Box 8, Folder 14)
  - Leo Brewer Issue, Manuscript B4, 221602 (Box 8, Folder 15)
  - Leo Brewer Issue, Manuscript B5, 221601 (Box 8, Folder 16)
  - Leo Brewer Issue, Manuscript B6, 221600 (Box 8, Folder 17)
  - Leo Brewer Issue, Manuscript B7, 221599 (Box 8, Folder 18)
  - Leo Brewer Issue, Manuscript B8, 221598 (Box 8, Folder 19)
  - Leo Brewer Issue, Manuscript B9, 221597 (Box 8, Folder 20)
  - Leo Brewer Issue, Manuscript B10, 221596 (Box 8, Folder 21)
  - Leo Brewer Issue, Manuscript B11, 221595 (Box 8, Folder 22)
  - Leo Brewer Issue, Manuscript B12, 221594 (Box 8, Folder 23)
  - Leo Brewer Issue, Manuscript B13, 221593 (Box 8, Folder 24)
  - Leo Brewer Issue, Manuscript B14, 221592 (Box 8, Folder 25)
  - Leo Brewer Issue, Manuscript B15, 221591 (Box 8, Folder 26)
  - Leo Brewer Issue, Manuscript B16, 221590 (Box 8, Folder 27)
  - Leo Brewer Issue, Manuscript B17, 221589 (Box 8, Folder 28)
  - Leo Brewer Issue, Manuscript B18, 221588 (Box 8, Folder 29)
  - Leo Brewer Issue, Manuscript B19, 221587 (Box 8, Folder 30)
  - Leo Brewer Issue, Manuscript B20, 221586 (Box 8, Folder 31)
  - Leo Brewer Issue, Manuscript B21, 221585 (Box 8, Folder 32)
  - Leo Brewer Issue, Manuscript B22, 221584 (Box 8, Folder 33)
  - Leo Brewer Issue, Manuscript B23, 221583 (Box 8, Folder 34)
  - Leo Brewer Issue, Manuscript B24, 221582 (Box 8, Folder 35)
  - Leo Brewer Issue, Manuscript B25, 221581 (Box 8, Folder 36)
  - Leo Brewer Issue, Manuscript B26, 221580 (Box 8, Folder 37)
  - Leo Brewer Issue, Manuscript B27, 221579 (Box 8, Folder 38)
  - Leo Brewer Issue, Manuscript B28, 221578 (Box 8, Folder 39)
  - Leo Brewer Issue, Miscellaneous, 221577 (Box 8, Folder 40)
  - Leo Brewer Issue, Proofs, Manuscripts B1-B4, 221576 (Box 8, Folder 41)
  - Leo Brewer Issue, Proofs, Manuscripts B7-B14, 221575 (Box 8, Folder 42)
  - Leo Brewer Issue, Proofs, Manuscripts B15-B22, 221574 (Box 8, Folder 43)
  - Leo Brewer Issue, Proofs, Manuscripts B23-B28, 221573 (Box 8, Folder 44)
  - Manuscripts in original # order, with associated years noted, 221521
    - 1-99 (1969, 1970, 1985, 1991, 1994), 221572 (Box 8, Folder 45)
    - 100-162 (1970-1971), 221571 (Box 8, Folder 46)
    - 163-173 (1971-1972), 221570 (Box 8, Folder 47)
    - 174-185 (1971-1972), 221569 (Box 8, Folder 48)
    - 186-199 (1972), 221568 (Box 8, Folder 49)
    - 200-210 (1972), 221567 (Box 9, Folder 1)
    - 211-220 (1972-1973), 221566 (Box 9, Folder 2)
    - 221-228 (1972-1973), 221565 (Box 9, Folder 3)
    - 229-239 (1973), 221564 (Box 9, Folder 4)
    - 240-249 (1973), 221563 (Box 9, Folder 5)
    - 250-259 (1973), 221562 (Box 9, Folder 6)
    - 260-269 (1973), 221561 (Box 9, Folder 7)
    - 270-279 (1973-1974), 221560 (Box 9, Folder 8)
    - 280-289 (1974), 221559 (Box 9, Folder 9)
    - 290-299 (1974-1975), 221558 (Box 9, Folder 10)
    - 300-309 (1974-1975), 221557 (Box 9, Folder 11)
    - 310-319 (1974-1975), 221556 (Box 9, Folder 12)
    - 320-329 (1975), 221555 (Box 9, Folder 13)
    - 330-349 (1975-1976), 221554 (Box 9, Folder 14)
    - 350-369 (1976-1977), 221553 (Box 9, Folder 15)
    - 370-379 (1977), 221552 (Box 9, Folder 16)
    - 380-399 (1977-1978), 221551 (Box 9, Folder 17)
    - 400-469 (1978-1979), 221550 (Box 9, Folder 18)
    - 470-479 (1979-1980), 221549 (Box 9, Folder 19)
    - 480-489 (1979-1981), 221548 (Box 9, Folder 20)
    - 490-499 (1980-1981), 221547 (Box 9, Folder 21)
    - 500-519 (1980-1981), 221546 (Box 9, Folder 22)
    - 520-529 (1981), 221545 (Box 9, Folder 23)
    - 530-539 (1981), 221544 (Box 9, Folder 24)
    - 540-549 (1981-1982, 1984), 221543 (Box 9, Folder 25)
    - 551-579 (1982-1983), 221542 (Box 9, Folder 26)
    - 580-589 (1983-1984), 221541 (Box 9, Folder 27)
    - 590-599 (1983-1984), 221540 (Box 9, Folder 28)
    - 600-609 (1984), 221539 (Box 10, Folder 1)
    - 610-619 (1984), 221538 (Box 10, Folder 2)
    - 620-629 (1985-1986), 221537 (Box 10, Folder 3)
    - 630-639 (1985-1987), 221536 (Box 10, Folder 4)
    - 640-659 (1986-1987), 221535 (Box 10, Folder 5)
    - 660-669 (1987-1988), 221534 (Box 10, Folder 6)
    - 670-689 (1988-1989), 221533 (Box 10, Folder 7)
    - 690-699 (1989), 221532 (Box 10, Folder 8)
    - 700-719 (1990-1991), 221531 (Box 10, Folder 9)
    - 720-729 (1991), 221530 (Box 10, Folder 10)
    - 730-789 (1991-1995), 221529 (Box 10, Folder 11)
    - Miscellaneous, 221528 (Box 10, Folder 12)
    - Miscellaneous Copyright Agreements, 221527 (Box 10, Folder 13)
    - Miscellaneous Correspondence, 221526 (Box 10, Folder 14)
    - Miscellaneous Reviews, 221525 (Box 10, Folder 15)
    - Notes, 221524 (Box 10, Folder 16)
    - Questionnaires, 221523 (Box 10, Folder 17)
    - Subscription Counts, 221522 (Box 10, Folder 18)
- Series VI: Marchem, Incorporated, 1972-1985, 221434
  Within the Marchem, Incorporated series are consulting files, an account register, and a checkbook. In addition, the series includes correspondence, consulting agreements, and fluorination books that show, in detail, testing methodologies and results.
  - Manuscripts in original # order, with associated years noted, 221435
    - 1-99 (1969, 1970, 1985, 1991, 1994), 221519 (Box 8, Folder 45)
    - 100-162 (1970-1971), 221518 (Box 8, Folder 46)
    - 163-173 (1971-1972), 221517 (Box 8, Folder 47)
    - 174-185 (1971-1972), 221516 (Box 8, Folder 48)
    - 186-199 (1972), 221515 (Box 8, Folder 49)
    - 200-210 (1972), 221514 (Box 9, Folder 1)
    - 211-220 (1972-1973), 221513 (Box 9, Folder 2)
    - 221-228 (1972-1973), 221512 (Box 9, Folder 3)
    - 229-239 (1973), 221511 (Box 9, Folder 4)
    - 240-249 (1973), 221510 (Box 9, Folder 5)
    - 250-259 (1973), 221509 (Box 9, Folder 6)
    - 260-269 (1973), 221508 (Box 9, Folder 7)
    - 270-279 (1973-1974), 221507 (Box 9, Folder 8)
    - 280-289 (1974), 221506 (Box 9, Folder 9)
    - 290-299 (1974-1975), 221505 (Box 9, Folder 10)
    - 300-309 (1974-1975), 221504 (Box 9, Folder 11)
    - 310-319 (1974-1975), 221503 (Box 9, Folder 12)
    - 320-329 (1975), 221502 (Box 9, Folder 13)
    - 330-349 (1975-1976), 221501 (Box 9, Folder 14)
    - 350-369 (1976-1977), 221500 (Box 9, Folder 15)
    - 370-379 (1977), 221499 (Box 9, Folder 16)
    - 380-399 (1977-1978), 221498 (Box 9, Folder 17)
    - 400-469 (1978-1979), 221497 (Box 9, Folder 18)
    - 470-479 (1979-1980), 221496 (Box 9, Folder 19)
    - 480-489 (1979-1981), 221495 (Box 9, Folder 20)
    - 490-499 (1980-1981), 221494 (Box 9, Folder 21)
    - 500-519 (1980-1981), 221493 (Box 9, Folder 22)
    - 520-529 (1981), 221492 (Box 9, Folder 23)
    - 530-539 (1981), 221491 (Box 9, Folder 24)
    - 540-549 (1981-1982, 1984), 221490 (Box 9, Folder 25)
    - 551-579 (1982-1983), 221489 (Box 9, Folder 26)
    - 580-589 (1983-1984), 221488 (Box 9, Folder 27)
    - 590-599 (1983-1984), 221487 (Box 9, Folder 28)
    - 600-609 (1984), 221486 (Box 10, Folder 1)
    - 610-619 (1984), 221485 (Box 10, Folder 2)
    - 620-629 (1985-1986), 221484 (Box 10, Folder 3)
    - 630-639 (1985-1987), 221483 (Box 10, Folder 4)
    - 640-659 (1986-1987), 221482 (Box 10, Folder 5)
    - 660-669 (1987-1988), 221481 (Box 10, Folder 6)
    - 670-689 (1988-1989), 221480 (Box 10, Folder 7)
    - 690-699 (1989), 221479 (Box 10, Folder 8)
    - 700-719 (1990-1991), 221478 (Box 10, Folder 9)
    - 720-729 (1991), 221477 (Box 10, Folder 10)
    - 730-789 (1991-1995), 221476 (Box 10, Folder 11)
    - Miscellaneous, 221475 (Box 10, Folder 12)
    - Miscellaneous Copyright Agreements, 221474 (Box 10, Folder 13)
    - Miscellaneous Correspondence, 221473 (Box 10, Folder 14)
    - Miscellaneous Reviews, 221472 (Box 10, Folder 15)
    - Notes, 221471 (Box 10, Folder 16)
    - Questionnaires, 221470 (Box 10, Folder 17)
    - Account Register, 1977-1981, 221469 (Box 11, Folder 1)
    - Appointment Book, 1986, 221468 (Box 11, Folder 2)
    - Bank Statement, 221467 (Box 11, Folder 3)
    - Boeing Aerospace, 221466 (Box 11, Folder 4)
    - Certainteed Corporation, 221465 (Box 11, Folder 5)
    - Checkbook, 1977-1983, 221464 (Box 11, Folder 6)
    - Chemical Economics Handbook, 221463 (Box 11, Folder 7)
    - Consulting and Licensing Agreements, 221462 (Box 11, Folder 8)
    - Correspondence, 221461 (Box 11, Folder 9)
    - Du Pont, 221460 (Box 11, Folder 10)
    - Fluorination Book 1, 1970-1972, 221459 (Box 11, Folder 11)
    - Fluorination Book 2, 1972-1974, 221458 (Box 11, Folder 12)
    - Fluorination Book 3, 1974-1976, 221457 (Box 11, Folder 13)
    - Fluorination Book 4, 1976-1981, 221456 (Box 11, Folder 14)
    - Fluorination Book 5, 1981-1983, 221455 (Box 11, Folder 15)
    - Fluorination Book 6, 1984-1987, 221454 (Box 11, Folder 16)
    - Laboratory Research Notebook, Reactions of Elementary Fluorine, Dr. R. B. Badachhape, 221453 (Box 11, Folder 17)
    - Laboratory Research Notebook, Fluorination, Dr. R. B. Badachhape, 221452 (Box 11, Folder 18)
    - Laboratory Research Notebook, High Pressure and Fluorination, Dr. R. B. Badachhape, 221451 (Box 11, Folder 19)
    - References for Thesis Const[ruction?], 221450 (Box 12, Folder 1)
    - Fluorine Products and Processes, 221449 (Box 12, Folder 2)
    - Kerr-McGee, 221448 (Box 12, Folder 3)
    - LTV Aerospace, 221447 (Box 12, Folder 4)
    - Meetings, Air Products, 221446 (Box 12, Folder 5)
    - Meetings, Ethyl Corporation, 221445 (Box 12, Folder 6)
    - Meetings, Kodak, 221444 (Box 12, Folder 7)
    - Meetings, Stratoflex, 221443 (Box 12, Folder 8)
    - Miscellaneous, 221442 (Box 12, Folder 9)
    - Powderless Surgical Gloves, 221441 (Box 12, Folder 10)
    - Proposals, 221440 (Box 12, Folder 11)
    - Schroeder v. Conoco, 221439 (Box 12, Folder 12)
    - Tax Documents, 221438 (Box 12, Folder 13)
    - Vought Corporation, 221437 (Box 12, Folder 14)
    - Vulcan Proposal, 221436 (Box 12, Folder 15)
- Series VII: Meetings, 1970-1988, 220856
  This series contains materials related to the many conferences and assemblies that Margrave attended in connection with his membership in associations, institutions, and organizations. Included are meeting agendas, minutes, programs, paper abstracts, as well as correspondence related to his many visiting chemistry lectures. Of particular note are two files related to Margrave's service on the 1980 presidential search committee for Texas Southern University.
  - 3M, December 11-12, 1983, 221433 (Box 13, Folder 1)
  - AAAS, February 20-25, 1977, 221432 (Box 13, Folder 2)
  - AAAS, March 29-30, 1984, 221431 (Box 13, Folder 3)
  - AAAS, November 12-13, 1970, February 22-23, 1971, 221430 (Box 13, Folder 4)
  - AAU, September 26, 1985, 221429 (Box 13, Folder 5)
  - Accurex, 221428 (Box 13, Folder 6)
  - ACS, April 1972, 221427 (Box 13, Folder 7)
  - ACS, August 28-September 1, 1972, 221426 (Box 13, Folder 8)
  - ACS, December 6-8, 1972, 221425 (Box 13, Folder 9)
  - ACS, August 26-31, 1973, 221424 (Box 13, Folder 10-11)
  - ACS, December 5-7, 1973, 221423 (Box 13, Folder 12)
  - ACS, February 14, 1974, 221422 (Box 13, Folder 13)
  - ACS, March 31-April 5, 1974, 221421 (Box 13, Folder 14-15)
  - ACS, September 8-13, 1974, 221420 (Box 13, Folder 16-17)
  - ACS, September 18, 1974, 221419 (Box 13, Folder 18)
  - ACS, December 9-11, 1974, 221418 (Box 13, Folder 19)
  - ACS, March 19, 1975, 221417 (Box 13, Folder 20)
  - ACS, April 6-11, 1975, 221416 (Box 13, Folder 21)
  - ACS, June 12-13, 1975, 221415 (Box 13, Folder 22)
  - ACS, August 24-29, 1975, 221414 (Box 13, Folder 23-24)
  - ACS, October 29-31, 1975, 221413 (Box 13, Folder 25)
  - ACS, April 4, 1976, 221412 (Box 13, Folder 26)
  - ACS, August 19, 1976, 221411 (Box 13, Folder 27)
  - ACS, August 29-September 3, 1976, 221410 (Box 13, Folder 28-29)
  - ACS, October 27-29, 1976, 221409 (Box 14, Folder 1)
  - ACS, February 4, 1977, 221408 (Box 14, Folder 2)
  - ACS, March 19-23, 1977, 221407 (Box 14, Folder 3)
  - ACS, August 28-September 2, 1977, 221406 (Box 14, Folder 4)
  - ACS, March 12-17, 1978, 221405 (Box 14, Folder 5)
  - ACS, April 20, 1978, 221404 (Box 14, Folder 6)
  - ACS, May 24, 1978, 221403 (Box 14, Folder 7)
  - ACS, September 11-16, 1978, 221402 (Box 14, Folder 8)
  - ACS, April 2-5, 1979, 221401 (Box 14, Folder 9)
  - ACS, September 9-14, 1979, 221400 (Box 14, Folder 10)
  - ACS, December 5-7, 1979, 221399 (Box 14, Folder 11)
  - ACS, March 23-28, 1980, 221398 (Box 14, Folder 12-13)
  - ACS, March 29-April 3, 1981, 221397 (Box 14, Folder 14-15)
  - ACS, August 23-28, 1981, 221396 (Box 14, Folder 16-17)
  - ACS, December 9-11, 1981, 221395 (Box 14, Folder 18)
  - ACS, March 29-April 2, 1982, 221394 (Box 14, Folder 19)
  - ACS, September 12-17, 1982, 221393 (Box 14, Folder 20)
  - ACS, September 16, 1982, 221392 (Box 14, Folder 21)
  - ACS, December 1-3, 1982, 221391 (Box 14, Folder 22)
  - ACS. March 20-25, 1983, 221390 (Box 14, Folder 23)
  - ACS, August 28-September 2, 1983, 221389 (Box 14, Folder 24)
  - ACS, April 8-12, 1984, 221388 (Box 15, Folder 1-2)
  - ACS, August 26-31, 1984, 221387 (Box 15, Folder 3)
  - ACS, December 5-7, 1984, 221386 (Box 15, Folder 4)
  - ACS, April 29-May 3, 1985, 221385 (Box 15, Folder 5)
  - ACS, April 13-18, 1986, 221384 (Box 15, Folder 6-7)
  - ACS, April 17, 1986 (includes the presentation "One Hundred Years of Fluorine Chemistry", 221383 (Box 15, Folder 8)
  - ACS, May 8, 1986, 221382 (Box 15, Folder 9)
  - ACS, September 7-12, 1986, 221381 (Box 15, Folder 10)
  - ACS, Fall 1986, 221380 (Box 15, Folder 11)
  - ACS, November 19-21, 1986, 221379 (Box 15, Folder 12)
  - ACS, April 5-10, 1987, 221378 (Box 15, Folder 13)
  - ACS, Awards Judging Team, March 14, 1985, 221377 (Box 15, Folder 14)
  - ACS, Conference on Carbon, July 17-22, 1983, 221376 (Box 15, Folder 15)
  - ACS, Division of Inorganic Chemistry, May 16-19, 1982, 221375 (Box 15, Folder 16)
  - ACS, Fluorine Conference, January 23-28, 1972, 221374 (Box 15, Folder 17)
  - ACS, Fluorine Conference, January 28-February 3, 1979, 221373 (Box 15, Folder 18)
  - ACS, Fluropolymer Conference, April 9-13, 1975, 221372 (Box 15, Folder 19)
  - ACS, Joint Technical Meeting, March 31, 1978, 221371 (Box 15, Folder 20)
  - ACS, Leo Wall Symposium, April 9-13, 1973, 221370 (Box 15, Folder 21)
  - ACS, New Applications to Fossil Fuels, April 13-18, 1986, 221369 (Box 15, Folder 22)
  - ACS, Notices, 221368 (Box 15, Folder 23)
  - ACS, Operation Interface, November 17, 1980, 221367 (Box 15, Folder 24)
  - ACS, Redistricting Chicago, September 8-13, 1985, 221366 (Box 15, Folder 25)
  - ACS, Report to U.S. Congress, October 24, 1973, 221365 (Box 15, Folder 26)
  - Advisory Committee to Texas Senate Committee on Business, June 6, 1984, 221364 (Box 15, Folder 27)
  - Advisory Committee to Texas Senate Committee on Business, July 13, 1984, 221363 (Box 15, Folder 28)
  - Advisory Committee to Texas Senate Committee on Business, August 1, 1984, 221362 (Box 15, Folder 29)
  - Advisory Committee to Texas Senate Committee on Business, October 9, 1984, 221361 (Box 15, Folder 30)
  - AEC, 221360 (Box 15, Folder 31)
  - AFOSR, Advisory Group JANAF, March 29-31, 1972, 221359 (Box 15, Folder 32)
  - AFOSR, Panel Review, March 16, 1974, 221358 (Box 15, Folder 33-34)
  - AFOSR, Research Evaluation Meeting, August 30, 1973, 221357 (Box 15, Folder 35)
  - AFOSR, Research Evaluation Meeting, September 12, 1974, 221356 (Box 15, Folder 36)
  - AFOSR, Research Evaluation Meeting, April 8, 1975, 221355 (Box 16, Folder 1-2)
  - AFOSR, Research Evaluation Meeting, September 26-27, 1975, 221354 (Box 16, Folder 3)
  - AFOSR, Research Evaluation Meeting, May 21, 1976, 221353 (Box 16, Folder 4)
  - AFOSR, Research Evaluation Meeting, November 19, 1976, 221352 (Box 16, Folder 5-6)
  - AFOSR, Research Evaluation Meeting, May 12-13, 1977, 221351 (Box 16, Folder 7-8)
  - AFOSR, Research Evaluation Meeting, November 17-18, 1977, 221350 (Box 16, Folder 9)
  - AFOSR, Symposia on Organosilicon, August 21-24, 1972, 221349 (Box 16, Folder 10)
  - AFWL, CFX, 221348 (Box 16, Folder 11)
  - AIC, May 15-18, 1974, 221347 (Box 16, Folder 12)
  - AIC, Miscellaneous, 221346 (Box 16, Folder 13)
  - AIEC, 221345 (Box 16, Folder 14)
  - Allied Chemical, August 11, 1972, 221344 (Box 16, Folder 15)
  - Allied Chemical, February 12, 1980, 221343 (Box 16, Folder 16)
  - Allied Chemical, February 23, 1981, 221342 (Box 16, Folder 17)
  - Amerigas, 221341 (Box 16, Folder 18)
  - Ames Laboratory USAEC, Review, 221340 (Box 16, Folder 19)
  - American Council on Education, 221339 (Box 16, Folder 20)
  - Annual Review of Physical Chemistry, Editorial Committee Meeting, 221338 (Box 16, Folder 21)
  - ANROTCCU, October 26-28, 1980, 221337 (Box 16, Folder 22)
  - ANROTCCU, September 27-29, 1981, 221336 (Box 16, Folder 23)
  - ANROTCCU, November 7-9, 1982, 221335 (Box 16, Folder 24)
  - ANROTCCU, October 6-8, 1983, 221334 (Box 16, Folder 25)
  - ANROTCCU, October 28-30, 1984, 221333 (Box 16, Folder 26)
  - ANROTCCU, October 4-6, 1985, 221332 (Box 16, Folder 27)
  - ARCS, October 12, 1984, 221331 (Box 16, Folder 28)
  - ARCS, Auction, October 18, 1985, 221330 (Box 16, Folder 29)
  - ARCS, Auction, January 30, 1987, 221329 (Box 16, Folder 30)
  - Argonne National Laboratory, May 4, 1976, 221328 (Box 16, Folder 31)
  - Argonne National Laboratory, High Temperature Science, April 4-6, 1977, 221327 (Box 16, Folder 32)
  - ARPA, 1971, 221326 (Box 17, Folder 1)
  - ARPA, 1973, 221325 (Box 17, Folder 2)
  - ARPA, July 5-29, 1978, 221324 (Box 17, Folder 3)
  - ARPA, Fluorine Handling, July 13, 1979, 221323 (Box 17, Folder 4)
  - ARPA, Solid Lubricants, July 23, 1979, 221322 (Box 17, Folder 5)
  - ARPA/MRC, July 5-7, 1978, 221321 (Box 17, Folder 6)
  - ASLE, 221320 (Box 17, Folder 7)
  - ASME, Energy Technology Conference, June 8, 1978, 221319 (Box 17, Folder 8)
  - ASME, Energy Technology Conference, November 5-9, 1978, 221318 (Box 17, Folder 9)
  - ASMS, February 14, 1973, 221317 (Box 17, Folder 10)
  - ASMS, May 20-25, 1973, 221316 (Box 17, Folder 11)
  - ASMS, May 19-24, 1974, 221315 (Box 17, Folder 12)
  - ASMS, May 25-30, 1975, 221314 (Box 17, Folder 13)
  - ASMS, May 9-14, 1976, 221313 (Box 17, Folder 14)
  - ASMS, May 29-June 3, 1977, 221312 (Box 17, Folder 15)
  - ASMS, May 27-June 1, 1984, 221311 (Box 17, Folder 16)
  - ASMS, May 1985, 221310 (Box 17, Folder 17)
  - ASMS, Board Meeting, July 22-23, 1974, 221309 (Box 17, Folder 18)
  - ASMS, Board Meeting, July 9-11, 1975, 221308 (Box 17, Folder 19)
  - Association of Texas Colleges, April 1, 1976, 221307 (Box 17, Folder 20)
  - Association of Texas Graduate Schools, April 4, 1974, 221306 (Box 17, Folder 21)
  - Association of Texas Graduate Schools, April 3, 1975, 221305 (Box 17, Folder 22)
  - Association of Texas Graduate Schools, March 31, 1977, 221304 (Box 17, Folder 23)
  - Association of Texas Graduate Schools, March 30, 1978, 221303 (Box 17, Folder 24)
  - Association of Texas Graduate Schools, April 2, 1981, 221302 (Box 17, Folder 25)
  - AWU, October 24, 1977, 221301 (Box 17, Folder 26)
  - AWU, April 18, 1980, 221300 (Box 17, Folder 27)
  - AWU, April 23-24, 1984, 221299 (Box 17, Folder 28)
  - AWU, April 23, 1985, 221298 (Box 17, Folder 29)
  - AWU, April 8, 1986, 221297 (Box 17, Folder 30)
  - BDM, January 6, 1983, 221296 (Box 17, Folder 31)
  - BDM/DARPA, December 16-17, 1982, 221295 (Box 17, Folder 32)
  - BDM/DARPA, UTRC/Laser Testing, April 20, 1983, 221294 (Box 17, Folder 33)
  - BDM/DARPA, LCMMD, January 10, 1985, 221293 (Box 17, Folder 34)
  - BDM/DARPA, LCMMD Workshop, July 20-22, 1983, 221292 (Box 17, Folder 35-36)
  - BDM, Laser Pyrolysis, September 20-21, 1982, 221291 (Box 17, Folder 37)
  - BDM, LCMMD, October 12-15, 1982, 221290 (Box 17, Folder 38)
  - BDM, LCMMD, January 31-February 2, 1984, 221289 (Box 17, Folder 39)
  - BDM, LCMMD, November 25, 1985, 221288 (Box 17, Folder 40)
  - BDM, LCMMD, April 21-22, 1986, 221287 (Box 17, Folder 41)
  - BDM, LCMMD Interim Report, March 8, 1983, 221286 (Box 17, Folder 42)
  - BDM, LCMMD Program, June 9, 1982, 221285 (Box 17, Folder 43)
  - BDM, LCMMD Review, March 20-21, 1984, 221284 (Box 17, Folder 44)
  - BDM, Steering Committee, May 15-16, 1985, 221283 (Box 17, Folder 45)
  - Calorimetry Conference, July 19-22, 1972, 221282 (Box 18, Folder 1)
  - Calorimetry Conference, June 13-15, 1973, 221281 (Box 18, Folder 2)
  - Calorimetry Conference, September 3-7, 1973, 221280 (Box 18, Folder 3)
  - Calorimetry Conference, July 16-19, 1975, 221279 (Box 18, Folder 4)
  - Calorimetry Conference, September 9-October 2, 1976, 221278 (Box 18, Folder 5)
  - Calorimetry Conference, July 6-8, 1977, 221277 (Box 18, Folder 6)
  - Calorimetry Conference, July 20-23, 1982, 221276 (Box 18, Folder 7)
  - CBTCUS, October 17, 1975, 221275 (Box 18, Folder 8)
  - CBTCUS, April 23, 1976, 221274 (Box 18, Folder 9)
  - CBTCUS, March 8, 1977, 221273 (Box 18, Folder 10)
  - CBTCUS, January 20, 1978, 221272 (Box 18, Folder 11)